question_data = [{"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "In the Shrek film franchise, Donkey is played by Eddie Murphy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Bill Cipher in the show Gravity Falls; is the good guy.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Nickelodeon rejected the pilot to Adventure Time.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Waylon Smithers from The Simpsons was originally black when he first appeared in the series.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Donald Duck played the role of Bob Cratchit in Disneys 1983 adaptation of A Christmas Carol.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations",
                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                                            "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Night on Bald Mountain was one of the musical pieces featured in Disneys 1940s film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Nutcracker Suite was one of the musical pieces featured in Disneys 1940s film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Blue Danube was one of the musical pieces featured in Disneys 1940s film Fantasia.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Snagglepuss was part of the Yogi Yahooies in the 1977 show Scoobys All-Star Laff-a-Lympics.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "In Avatar: The Last Airbender and The Legend of Korra, Lavabending is a specialized bending technique of Firebending.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]
